All right guys, so Bitcoin only has 600
days left. Let's keep it real. It only
has 600 days left. I'm going to talk
about why. Trust me, I'm going to get to
it, but we got to tell the story first.
You don't know who I am. I'm Travaun
James. I've been in crypto since 2015,
so that means I've seen pretty much
every pump from back here. This is where
I got into crypto at, around $200. I got
in at a bottom. I've been around, I've
seen this all play out over and over
again. So, my knowledge base is higher
than yours. I'm sorry.
It's just higher. I know more.
Crypto is my thing. So, I rode it from
300 BitConnect all the way to 20,000,
and we had our first pullback. And funny
enough, here is where I famously drew
this triangle on this chart, and I made
jokes about how Bitcoin was going to
fall again. Now, being that was my first
rodeo, I was wrong. And we actually
broke out, really nearly tested new
highs. And then we have the COVID
breakdown right here, under the 200.
Now, keep an eye on this trend line to
the left I've drawn. Clearly had the
breakdown below the 200 during COVID.
Epic buying opportunity. It's funny, I
had a friend who bought Bitcoin here,
and I told him that his buying had me
concerned, and that was actually a top.
Now, he still has his Bitcoin, though,
which is actually pretty dope. But, I
also remember during this period right
here, we had a meet up. He was really
panicking because he bought a a lot. So,
I was telling him, "Don't sell, just
hold on." And it was the right play. He
held on, we held on, and we got to new
highs here. 55, made a new top. And if
you go on this channel right here, the
one that you're on, you can actually go
back to this period of time. I don't
know when it was, but I pretty much
called the top, and I got out of crypto.
We didn't get out, but, you know, took
profits to secure my comfort through the
bear market, which inevitably will come.
And it came. Now, looking at these
moving averages, you can kind of see the
little bit of whipsaw, but once we got
this second bearish cross on the 13 34,
we crashed down to the 200 under 200
here. Nice recovery and crypto just went
up and up and up and well Bitcoin just
went up and up and up and up and up and
up. And then we have a couple of dips on
the 13 34. Not quite a cross there.
But then we got our first bearish cross
here and that was the one. That was the
bearish cross. We actually had one back
here. So you had your warning, another
close call and then there's your
confirmation.
Bearish cross on the 13 34. Couldn't get
back above this support line that was
drawn back here and then actually, I
also have a post on my Twitter which is
pretty recent because I don't tweet much
now. But if you go back to around this
time period, I said I was selling again
because everybody was so excited. So,
sold to comfort myself for times like
right now where Bitcoin breaks down,
moves up a little bit, hits resistance
at the 13, crashes again, moves up,
breaks through the 13, but doesn't quite
make it to the 34, so it rolls over
again and then we're back under the 13
hitting support. Now, where do we go
from here? Well, I'm here to tell you it
doesn't matter, okay? It doesn't matter
because Bitcoin only has 600 days left,
all right? Let me talk about why. So,
let's look at one of my favorite charts,
Bitcoin stock-to-flow. Now, this is the
chart that has kept me in crypto the
entire time, okay? If it weren't for
this chart, I honestly don't think I
would be where I am if it weren't for
this chart. So, what is this chart?
Well, did you know Bitcoin has these
things called halvings, guys? Every 4
years Bitcoin has a block halving,
meaning that the amount of Bitcoin that
they're mining drops in half, okay? So,
do you understand what that means? That
means that there are going to be less
Bitcoin coming onto the market. There's
already only 21 million of them. You
guys need to get off Twitter, get off X,
get out of the comment sections, get
your heads out of the sand. You guys do
this every single cycle, man, and it's
really amazing to watch you guys just
fud. Michael Saylor sold 32 Bitcoin and
now the market is just "Oh, it's over."
If I wanted to force the market down or
if I wanted to buy something cheap,
right, and I wanted to spook the market,
if I really wanted to sell, what if I
had 200,000 of a coin, right, and I sold
32 of them, do you think I'm really
trying to make money there? That's not a
make money type of move. That is a
manipulative type of move. That is a a
gesture. It's a gesture to the market to
get it to do something. But, the last
time Michael Saylor sold Bitcoin
was back here, guys.
It was literally back here.
December 2022. This is the last time
Michael Saylor sold Bitcoin. And I don't
want to focus too much on him, but it's
just kind of been in the topic lately.
But, guys, you got to stop it paying
attention to that stuff. There's only
one chart you need to look at, and it's
this one right here. This is the Bitcoin
stock-to-flow. And like I said, if it
wasn't for this chart, I probably
wouldn't even be in crypto anymore. But,
what it does is it displays the Bitcoin
price over the amount of days till the
next halving. And what you'll start to
see when you look at this chart is a a
simple the most simple obvious thing
that is so obvious that it can't be
true, but it always turns out to be
true. And that is when it's 600 when
it's 400 to 600 days until the next
halving, that's when you buy Bitcoin.
And if you do that, you're going to have
a good time. Now, the first time we had
a green indicator was the first halving.
So, we can't we're not going to really
go off of that one. But, you see that it
turns green, and then right when it
switches from blue to red, that's when
the halving happens. That's when the
amount of Bitcoin per block lessens
half. Right now, we're printing three
Bitcoin every 15 minutes. So, three
Bitcoin every block. And in about 600
days, it's going to drop from three
Bitcoin to 1.5. And then from 1.5 to
7.something. Okay, it's going to keep on
halving until all the Bitcoin are mined.
So, we got three Bitcoin hitting the
market every 15 minutes. So, that's
about a little over 200,000
every 15 minutes. $200,000 worth of
Bitcoin. And then it's going to decrease
from 1.5. So, if the price stayed the
same, a little over 100,000 every 15
minutes. So, it's going to be less,
right? So, if there's less to sell, that
signals to the market that it's becoming
more and more scarce. So, every time we
have this event right here, that's blue
to red, the market pumps afterwards.
Okay? When you look back in time, you
always see that it was during the green
period that you should have been buying.
Well, another thing we notice is when it
turns orange. When it goes from orange
to yellow, that's when you want to start
taking profit. We got a long way until
the next halving. We got a lot of
cleaning up to do. Go ahead and sell.
Take some profit. Come back when it's
green. So, if you do that when it's
yellow, you'll do pretty good. So, we
see again in 2013, that's when everybody
was excited. I hadn't heard about
Bitcoin yet, but I hear that it was the
same type of bubble scenario where
everybody was into it, and it was the
most popular thing ever. It's going to
change the world, and then the bubble
pops, and we start to fall. And we
notice that we get closer and it starts
to turn a little green. Starts seeing
more and more green. Green, green,
green. Now, this is around where I
started to get into the Bitcoin. I must
say luckily, because I hadn't heard
about it until this period. So, I
started to get into the Bitcoin during
this green period. More and more. So, if
you're buying Bitcoin through all of
this green right here, you imagine that.
Bitcoin is $200. You're just buying
Bitcoin just a dollar a day. Just buying
Bitcoin. Point
.01 BTC a day, right? And we're just
accumulating and then we start seeing
dark green. We're getting closer and
closer. Around 200 days, it's turning
blue, blue, blue, and then we have
the halving happens and we reset the
counter 1,400 more days. And what does
the market do? I remember and I actually
remember this time when the halving
happened, the newer guys like myself
were kind of expecting like this
magical, you know, thing that where the
price just pumps up and it actually
dumped after the halving, which was
actually pretty scary. But, if you stuck
to your guns and just listen to the OGs,
just listen to the OGs, man. That's
really all you got to do. Listen to the
OGs who have been in That's me, man.
I've been around. I've seen this. Find
you an OG who's been around at least
long as me and just listen to him. And
then we have the halving and it's like,
don't Don't Once you're red, don't sell
yet. Just hold on. Orange, orange,
yellow, and then we have our next top.
That's not even the top. Then we have
BitConnect. Yellow, yellow, yellow,
you're just taking profit. The same
You're just doing the opposite of what
you were doing back here. Selling a
dollar a day or whatever, $10 a day,
$100 a day, whatever. Just DCA'ing
into cash and just waiting for that
timer to hit 600 days. Then then we
start turning green and we look at the
market. Green, green, green, green,
green.
It's accumulating. Oh, it dropped again.
Oh, no.
But, still green, bro. It's green.
That's what it's supposed to do when
it's green.
You're supposed to be buying. Green, go.
You know, think about it. Green means
go. You're just buying, buying, buying,
and then we start to turn blue again. We
actually have the dip for COVID, just
terrifying, but it's blue. Halving's
coming up. It's all irrelevant. And we
turn red and boom goes the dynamite. And
we're red and we're off to the races
So, then we go into 2020 bubble, same
thing. A little bit off, a little early
on the top, but it actually ran up again
and gave you another exit. But, if you
stick to the plan where it's orange,
yellow,
you know, during that time it's good to
start taking profit. And here we go
again, yellow and then it turns green.
And what do you do when it turns green?
You start buying. It's the same thing
over and over, man.
It's the And every You know what's funny
about this? Is every time I talk about
this, there's somebody saying this time
is different. It's never different,
guys. It's programmed, it's calculated,
it's not going to change. That's never
going to change. And the thing that's
also going to stay the same is people
are going to always doubt that it's
going to stay the same. And I'm not. I'm
going to just stick with this. Green,
buy buy buy buy buy buy buy buy buy buy.
And people always say, "Well, Bitcoin's
multiplier is not going to go up much."
Listen, if you bought Bitcoin down here
at 15, you nearly got a 10X. If you
bought Bitcoin at the bottom, you buy at
the bottoms. People are measuring from
the from top to top. You're supposed to
measure measure from bottom to top, you
know, cuz if you're if you're especially
if you're buying at the bottoms. So,
buying when it's green, accumulate
accumulate accumulate. And then we start
to turn blue, start to turn blue. People
start to already price that in. Blue
blue blue blue.
And then, boop.
Halving. And sometimes it goes up after,
sometimes it goes down. This time it
kind of moved sideways, but eventually
it
I mean, you got us you got to ride it
out. There it goes.
Orange to 125
and then the yellow. You start seeing my
tweets. Guys,
I hate to say this, but you know, it's
going down, all right? Long story short.
And everybody's like,
First few couple people like, "Oh,
you're an idiot."
Guess what happens? Turns yellow. I just
stick with it. I don't FOMO back in. I
don't follow the hype. I just stick to
my plan, and it turns green.
And here we are, June 2nd, Michael
Saylor selling his Bitcoin. And look at
me, over here buying Bitcoin every
single day without any breaks. Actually,
on days like today where it's pretty
much crashing and you guys are crapping
your pants, I'm buying more than usual.
>> [laughter]
>> And I'm going to do that every day for
the next 600 days. And all I got to do
is think about how much will I have if I
do that for 600 days. So, if you do a
dollar every day, you have $600 worth of
Bitcoin in 600 days. $10, that's $6,000.
$100, that's $60,000. $1,000, that's
$600,000 in Bitcoin. $10,000, that's
$6,000,000 in Bitcoin.
Over the span of
60 600 days.
Just stick to the plan. And all the
other cryptos, Ethereum, sure. Solana,
sure. BNB, sure. Tron, sure. Maybe get
those, too. But you just don't have the
predictability
with those as you do for Bitcoin. And
that's pretty much the conclusion I've
come to is that this is so predictable
that I can just stick to this. I know
there's always the first one. As long as
there's no quantum computing scare,
which they've been talking about that
since I got into Bitcoin. It's always
quantum computers. It's always Bitcoin's
dying. It's not dying. Buy from the
lows. It's a free 10x every time. Do you
think the dollar is going to go down in
value? Uh, yeah. So, maybe buy some
Bitcoin. It's not like Bitcoin's going
to underperform the dollar. It's going
to outperform the dollar. So, at
minimum, just buy Bitcoin. It's like so
obvious. Um it's so obvious, it's
frustrating. But, I actually am buying
some altcoins. I talk about the altcoins
on my member videos. More of the, you
know, in the trenches plays, the yield
plays, the earning, the blockchain
certificate of deposit space. That's the
type stuff I'm into. If you want to see
me talk about that stuff, become a
member, and I will talk to you guys in
the next one. Peace.